# Jacob Hawkins

#### Computer Science Graduate

Highly motivated computer science graduate with 6 months of programming internship and over 3 years of customer service experience seeking an IT identity and access management role. Equipped with a strong technical background and a commitment to delivering exceptional service, I am excited to make a meaningful contribution to your organization's success.

🔀 jacohawk@yahoo.com



(309) 642-4582



Minneapolis



in linkedin.com/in/jacohawk

Time management

Independent worker

**SOFT SKILLS** 



#### **EDUCATION**

#### Computer Science Illinois Central College

08/2020 - 05/2023

Courses Completed

- Web Development using HTML, CSS, PHP, and JavaScript
- Business Use of Social Media

Peoria. II

- Web Server and Web Application Security
- Web Content Management Systems, SEO, and Analytics



## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

#### Web Development

Customer service

Troubleshooting

Functional collaborator

HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript, WordPress, Web Security

#### Tools

Microsoft Suite, Google Suite, Project Management Approaches (Waterfall, Agile), Wireframing



## **CERTIFICATES**

World Organization of Webmasters Certified Web Developer Associate (08/2021 - 05/2023)



#### REFERENCES

Curtis Geiger "Lead Web Data Engineer" curtis.geiger@linkup.com

## WORK EXPERIENCE

### Web Programming Intern LinkUp

10/2022 - Present

Minneapolis, MN

Peoria, IL

LinkUp is a job market data company that tracks job market trends from over 70,000 different companies across the world.

#### Tasks & Responsibilities

- Fix, create, or update the code of the web scrapers according to client needs
- Communicate with the data quality team to ensure the accuracy of all data scraped
- Work alone or with fellow programmers to solve high priority requests from clients
- Finish up projects and tasks as directed in a timely manner

#### Meat Market Assistant Service Manager Hy-Vee

04/2021 - 08/2022

Tasks & Responsibilities

Take and fulfill customer orders in a courteous and timely manner

- Maintain the supply in the fresh meat case as well as the merchandising refrigerators as needed
- Communicate with managers and other associates in order to meet daily goals
- Train new associates to the standards of the lead service manager